popunder.net 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy

**Statistics (24h)**

**Latest news**

**13 of May 2015**   
Dear advertisers,  
Popunder.net network has a new feature - downloading statistics in the excel ! 

**02 of April 2015**   
Dear users,   
today advertising network Popunder.net is 8 years old!   
Hurry up to get [gifts](http://popunder.net/main/pages/birthday/)! 

**27 of February 2015**   
Dear publishers,   
in network Popunder.net been updated system domains of your code.  
Get it and reinstall on your site! 

This Privacy Policy is personal information (hereinafter - Policy) applies to all information that "Weblink" ltd and / or its affiliates, including all persons belonging to the same group with Weblink ltd (hereinafter - Popunder) can get from user during use of Popunder services.

**Using Popunder Services means unconditional acceptance of the user with this Policy and specified in its terms of its treatment of personal information; if you disagree with these conditions, the user must refrain from using the Services.**

**1\. Users personal information, received and processed by Popunder**   
1.1. In this Policy under the "users personal information" refers to:   
1.1.1. Personal information that user provides about himself independently at registration (creating an account) or during use of the Services, including personal data. Mandatory to provide the services information is highlighted in a special way. Other information provided by the user's discretion.   
1.2. Popunder generally does not validate personal information provided by users, and does not have control over their capacity. However Popunder comes from the fact that the user provides valid and sufficient personal information as prompted in the registration form, and maintains this information up to date. Consequences of misreporting defined in the User Agreement services (http://popunder.net/main/pages/oferta_web/).

**2\. Goal for collection and processing of users personal information**   
2.1. Popunder collects and stores only the personal data that is necessary to provide services (execution of agreements with users).   
2.2. Popunder can use user's personal information for the following purposes:   
2.2.1. To identify parties of agreements and contracts with Popunder;   
2.2.2. Giving user a personalized service;   
2.2.3. Communication with the user, including notifications, requests and information regarding the use of the Services, and processing requests and applications from the user;   
2.2.4. Improving the quality of service, ease of use, the development of new services;   
2.2.5. Targeting advertising materials;   
2.2.6. Conducting statistical and other studies based on anonymous data.

**3\. Conditions processing personal information of the user and its transfer to third parties**   
3.1. Popunder may transfer the user's personal information to third parties in the following cases:   
3.1.1. User consented to such actions;   
3.1.2. The transfer is necessary in the framework of the use of some specific services or to provide services to the user;   
3.1.3. Transmission provided by applicable law under the statutory procedures;   
3.1.4. This transmission takes place in the sale or other transfer of the business (in whole or in part), while to the purchaser assumes all obligations to comply with the terms of this Policy with respect to personal information received by him;   
3.1.5. In order to ensure protection of the rights and legitimate interests of third parties Popunder or in cases when the user violates the Terms of Service (http://popunder.net/main/pages/oferta_web/) or the rules of the network (http://popunder.net/ main / srules /).

**4\. Changing user personal information**   
4.1. User can at any time change (update, supplement) personal information and the parameters of its confidentiality by using the edit function of personal data in your account.   
4.2. User can also remove them provided within a specific account personal information by sending a request to support.

5\. **Measures taken to protect users' personal information**   
Popunder take the necessary and sufficient technical and organizational measures to protect personal information of the user from unauthorized or accidental access, destruction, modification, blocking, copying, distribution, as well as other illegal actions of third parties with her.

6\. **Changing Privacy Policy.**   
Popander has the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. When changes are made in the latest the date of last update. The new edition of the Policy shall come into force from the moment it is submitted, unless otherwise provided in the new version of the Policy. The current edition is at http://popunder.net/main/pages/privacy_policy/
